<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>about on constantly walking</title>
    <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in about on constantly walking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:35:37 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://g-w-matthews.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wanikani goods</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:36:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/</guid>
      <description>Wanikani has been a great way to study the kanji. What is also great about it, is the open data framework that it employs, enabling anyone who joins to get access to a huge data set of kanji, readings, meanings, mnenomics, levels in WK, JLPT, JOYO, etc. This data can be used for all kinds of purposes &amp;ndash; I have used it as input for various projects including:
 A mini kanji dictionary, with kanji sorted by the main onyomi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shirokuma Cafe</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/shirokuma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 09:35:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/shirokuma/</guid>
      <description>This classic, mildly absurdist anime series centered on a cafe run by a polar bear has been a big part of my language immersion strategy. As part of this effort I extracted the audio into small chunks and combined it with Japanese subtitles so you can get a combination of listening and reading practice in your browser where a tool like Yomichan or ichi.moe can be used to look up kanji or grammar that you don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 14:07:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Hacking Education Philosophy lives in dialogue. Our networked world offers many free and open ways of enagaging in dialogue. Networked doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to mean free, of course, as we all know in the age of monetized data streams. But some minor coding skills and a willingness to poke around under the digital hood can help keep it free and open for us all. That&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;ll see in my work past, present and future - open source!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Choice</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/a-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 13:06:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/a-choice/</guid>
      <description>Our currently interesting times are also very instructive, if only we can find the willingness to heed this instruction. As in other critical moments we are faced with a stark choice: do we acknowledge the full gravity of our situation? This would mean opening our imaginations to some pretty horrifying scenes &amp;ndash; hospitals overflowing again in more places than earlier this year, many more long term illnesses among us and premature death for thousands more of our friends, neighbors and family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By Way of a First Post</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 22:40:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
This is my official first blog post and I have been hemming and hawing a bit about what I&amp;rsquo;d like to write about. I probably won&amp;rsquo;t get very far with this but at least I&amp;rsquo;ll use it to mention a few things that I have been thinking about lately and that I might take the time to pursue a bit further. In no particular order, here are some things that have been on my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:07:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m George Matthews &amp;ndash; welcome to my blog! I am a philosophy professor who also likes to mess around with code. I have finally decided to create my own website. You&amp;rsquo;ll find here some things I have been working on lately in connection with courses I teach, and maybe if I can sit still long enough, occasional blog posts. Check out my CV.
This site is built with a static site generator called hugo which takes a collection of pages written basically as text files and turns them into a full-fledged website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science or Superstition</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:37:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent years I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching a course at Plymouth State University called &amp;ldquo;Science or Superstition.&amp;rdquo; This is a general education course that explores the history and philosophy of science, as well as the ways we tend to get things wrong when we attempt to explain and describe the world around us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:37:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In addition to ethics I also regularly teach Introduction to Philosophy online at Penn College. In spite of the fact that this course can only skim the surface of philosophical debate and analysis I never get bored with this course.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethics</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:35:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/ethics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching Ethics courses online at the Pennsylvania College of Technology for about twenty years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
