<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>about on constantly walking</title>
    <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in about on constantly walking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 09:35:37 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://g-w-matthews.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kanji Book</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/kanji-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 17:05:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/kanji-book/</guid>
      <description>This started out as an attempt to sort kanji by readings and ended up as a handbound reference book with all of the wanikani kanji, sorted by the first mostly onyomi reading.
There are two ways to print these.
 As full sized sheets to be bound on the long edge. Printed with plain font or with the stroke order font. As smaller pages to be printed in signatures and bound in a book using any number of hand binding techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waniakani Vocabulary</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/vocabulary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 17:00:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/vocabulary/</guid>
      <description>Wanikani uses a structured repetition system as the backbone of its approach to teaching the kanji. To help reinforce the readings it also has a ton of vocabulary to learn. To help me keep track of this vocubulary and get some extra reading practice I have created some printable vocabulary sheets. Think of these as cheat sheets or study aids rather than as flashcards.
 Wankikani vocabulary, levels 1 &amp;ndash; 20 Wankikani vocabulary, levels 21 &amp;ndash; 40 Wankikani vocabulary, levels 41 &amp;ndash; 60  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Practice</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/writing-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 17:36:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/wanikani-goods/writing-practice/</guid>
      <description>These writing practice sheets are intended as clear, efficient and clutter-free printable worksheets for practicing japanese writing with a pen, pencil, brush or brush pen. They have no english translations, and in the case of kanji, just a single, often onyomi reading. The point here is focusing on the character, keeping out english clutter and not including all linguistic information you might want about the item.
kana  ひらがな / a4 paper ひらがな / a4 paper, smaller characters カタカナ / a4 paper カタカナ / a4 paper, smaller characters  kanji These grew out of my use of Wanikani and online (paid) service for learning a great many kanji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shirokuma Cafe</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/shirokuma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 09:35:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E/shirokuma/</guid>
      <description>This classic, mildly absurdist anime series centered on a cafe run by a polar bear has been a big part of my language immersion strategy. As part of this effort I extracted the audio into small chunks and combined it with Japanese subtitles so you can get a combination of listening and reading practice in your browser where a tool like Yomichan or ichi.moe can be used to look up kanji or grammar that you don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 14:07:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Hacking Education Philosophy lives in dialogue and our networked world offers many free and open ways of enagaging in dialogue. Networked doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to mean free, though as we all know in the age of monetized data streams. But some minor hacking skills can help keep it free for us all. That&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;ll see in my work past, present and future.
Recent work:    Science or Superstition : course textbook and student blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Choice</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/a-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 13:06:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/a-choice/</guid>
      <description>Our currently interesting times are also very instructive, if only we can find the willingness to heed this instruction. As in other critical moments we are faced with a stark choice: do we acknowledge the full gravity of our situation? This would mean opening our imaginations to some pretty horrifying scenes &amp;ndash; hospitals overflowing again in more places than earlier this year, many more long term illnesses among us and premature death for thousands more of our friends, neighbors and family members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By Way of a First Post</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 22:40:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
This is my official first blog post and I have been hemming and hawing a bit about what I&amp;rsquo;d like to write about. I probably won&amp;rsquo;t get very far with this but at least I&amp;rsquo;ll use it to mention a few things that I have been thinking about lately and that I might take the time to pursue a bit further. In no particular order, here are some things that have been on my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 14:07:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m George Matthews &amp;ndash; welcome to my blog! I am a philosophy professor who also likes to mess around with websites, which I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly used for classes I teach. I have finally decided to create my own website. You&amp;rsquo;ll find here some things I have been working on lately in connection with courses I teach, and maybe if I can sit still long enough, occasional blog posts. Check out my CV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Slideshows</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/science/science-slideshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 17:36:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/science/science-slideshows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is all pretty self-explanatory &amp;ndash; these are some slideshows, produced once again with xaringan and R-Studio and open for reuse and remixing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethics Slideshows</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/ethics/ethics-slideshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 17:29:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/ethics/ethics-slideshows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are the latest versions of online teaching materials for a distance learning ethics course I have been teaching for the last (&lt;em&gt;gasp!!&lt;/em&gt;) 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro Slideshows</title>
      <link>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/intro/intro-slideshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 16:43:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://g-w-matthews.com/edu/intro/intro-slideshows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These slideshows were created for use in on online Introduction to Philosophy course.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
